clubdistrict.com 2017-12-14

# Privacy Policy

#### ClubDistrict.com Privacy Policy:

CLUBDISTRICT.COM ensures its members and visitors retain their privacy while they take advantage of all ClubDistrict.com has to offer. We are committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful, safe, online experience that you can get anywhere. If you have questions about this, please Contact Us.

Email: If you feel you have received an unsolicited email from ClubDistrict.com, it may be due to the following reasons:

  * You may have been referred to ClubDistrict.com by a friend of yours.
  * You may have been referred to ClubDistrict.com by another web site because you expressed an interest in a service we may offer.
  * You may have been referred to ClubDistrict.com by another company, who maintains an email listing of your name, seeking promotional services from ClubDistrict.com.

ClubDistrict.com gives you the opportunity to unsubscribe from our email list by following the unsubscribe instruction on the bottom of the mailing.

As of December 15, 2014, Trepster, LLC. (“ClubDistrict” or “we”) operates ClubDistrict.com. This Privacy Policy describes ClubDistrict’s use and sharing of personal information (“PI”-- your full name, email address, mailing address, telephone number, or credit card number) that Members voluntarily provide to ClubDistrict when they register (also known as “Registration PII”). The Term “User” refers to a Visitor or a Member. This Privacy Policy applies to the services offered by ClubDistrict, including any ClubDistrict-branded URL (the “ClubDistrict Website”), mobile technologies, and any other features, content, or applications offered from time to time by ClubDistrict in connection with the ClubDistrict Website (collectively, the “ClubDistrict Services”). The ClubDistrict Services are hosted in the United States.

The ClubDistrict Website is a general audience site and does not knowingly collect PI from children under 13 years of age.

From time to time ClubDistrict may modify this Privacy Policy to reflect industry initiatives or changes in the law, our PI collection and use practices, the features of the ClubDistrict Services, or technology, and such modifications shall be effective upon posting by ClubDistrict on the ClubDistrict Website. Your continued use of the ClubDistrict Services after ClubDistrict posts a revised Privacy Policy signifies your acceptance of the revised Privacy Policy. It is therefore important that you review this Privacy Policy regularly to ensure you are updated as to any changes. If ClubDistrict materially changes its practices regarding collection or use of your PI, your PI will continue to be governed by the Policy under which it was collected unless you have been provided notice of, and have not objected to, the change.

#### COLLECTION AND SUBMISSION OF PI AND NON-PI ON CLUBDISTRICT

General. When ClubDistrict collects PI from you it is because you are voluntarily submitting Registration PI to us in order to register as a Member of ClubDistrict. ClubDistrict may also collect PI from you if you choose to participate in ClubDistrict Services activities like sweepstakes, contests, and surveys, because you want us to furnish you with products, services, newsletters, or information, or in connection with content or suggestions you submit to ClubDistrict for review.

In addition, ClubDistrict collects other non-PI including IP address, aggregate user data, and browser type. This data is used to manage and improve the ClubDistrict Services, track usage, and for security purposes.

ClubDistrict Members may also choose to provide or store non-PI information in their profiles, including but not limited to date of birth, interests, hobbies, lifestyle choices, groups with whom they are affiliated (schools, companies), videos and/or pictures, private messages, bulletins or personal statements (collectively “Profile Information”). The Profile Information in a Member’s profile is provided at his or her sole discretion.

ClubDistrict Members can change their Registration PI and Profile Information at any time and can control how Visitors, other Members and ClubDistrict communicate with them by controlling their account settings, available within the “Edit Profile” portion of their ClubDistrict profile. Link to Account Settings.

Cookies. Cookies are small bits of information that ClubDistrict places on your computer. ClubDistrict uses cookies to identify your Internet browser, store Users’ preferences, and determine whether you have installed the enabling software needed to access certain material on the ClubDistrict Services. Data in cookies may be read to authenticate user sessions or provide services.

Third party advertisements displayed on ClubDistrict Services may also contain cookies set by Internet advertising companies or advertisers (known as “third party cookies”). ClubDistrict does not control these third party cookies and Users of the ClubDistrict Services should check the privacy policy of the Internet advertising company or advertiser to see whether and how it uses cookies. See the “Notice” section below for more information on customized advertising on ClubDistrict. A pixel tag is a tiny image inserted in a webpage and used to record the number and types of views for that page. ClubDistrict may allow third party pixel tags to be present on ClubDistrict Services for purposes of advertising, providing services or data and statistics collection.

You can program your computer to warn you each time a cookie is being sent, block third party cookies or block all cookies. However, by blocking all cookies you may not have access to certain features on the ClubDistrict Services.

#### NOTICE: CLUBDISTRICT WILL PROVIDE YOU WITH NOTICE ABOUT ITS PI COLLECTION PRACTICES

When you voluntarily provide PI to ClubDistrict, we will make sure you are informed about who is collecting the information, how and why the information is being collected and the types of uses ClubDistrict will make of the information to the extent it is being used in a manner that differs from what is allowed pursuant to this Privacy Policy.

At the time you provide your PI, ClubDistrict will notify you of your options regarding our use of your PI (See “Choice” below). Except as described in this Privacy Policy, ClubDistrict will not share your PI with third parties unless you have given ClubDistrict permission to do so (See “Use” below).

ClubDistrict Services may be linked to Internet sites operated by other companies. ClubDistrict Services may also carry advertisements from other companies. ClubDistrict is not responsible for the privacy practices of websites or other services operated by third parties that are linked to or integrated with the ClubDistrict Services or for the privacy practices of third party Internet advertising companies. Once you leave ClubDistrict Services via such a link, access a third party application (such as widgets) or click on an advertisement, you should check the applicable privacy policy of the third party or advertiser site to determine, among other things, how they will handle any PI they collect from you.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here.

ClubDistrict Services may also be linked to sites operated by companies affiliated with. Users who visit those Affiliated Company sites should still refer to their separate privacy policies and practices, which may differ in some respects from this Privacy Policy.

ClubDistrict may use cookies and similar tools to customize the content and advertising you receive based on the Profile Information you have provided. Profile Information you provide in structured profile fields or questions, information you add to open-ended profile fields and questions and other non-PI about you may also be used to customize the online ads you encounter to those we believe are aligned with your interests. For example, based on your music interests we might display an advertisement to make sure you are advised when your favorite band is coming to town. The information used for this feature does not provide your PI or identify you as an individual to third parties.

Some of the advertisements that appear on ClubDistrict Services may also be delivered to you by third party Internet advertising companies. These companies utilize certain technologies to deliver advertisements and marketing messages and to collect non-PI about your visit to or use of ClubDistrict Services, including information about the ads they display, via a cookie placed on your computer that reads your IP address.

Third party applications (such as widgets) created by third party developers may also be available on the ClubDistrict Services. Third party applications are small bits of software, often with interactivity, that can be installed into Members’ profiles or shared with other Users. However, ClubDistrict does not control the third party developers, and cannot dictate their actions. When a Member engages with a third party application, that Member is interacting with the third party developer, not with ClubDistrict. ClubDistrict encourages Members not to provide PI to the third party’s application unless the Member knows the party with whom it is interacting.

#### CHOICE: CLUBDISTRICT WILL PROVIDE YOU WITH CHOICES ABOUT THE USE OF YOUR PI

Except as described in this Privacy Policy, ClubDistrict will get your permission before we use the PI you provide to us in a way that is inconsistent with the purpose for which it was submitted or share your PI with third parties that are not affiliated with ClubDistrict.

#### USE: CLUBDISTRICT'S USE OF PI

ClubDistrict will only use the PI you provide under this Privacy Policy in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy. If ClubDistrict obtains PI from a third party, such as a business partner, our use of that information is also governed by this Privacy Policy.

In order to locate other ClubDistrict Members that you may already know in the physical world, ClubDistrict allows Users to search for Members using Registration PI (i.e., full name or email address). ClubDistrict also allows Users to browse for certain Profile Information in order to help connect with Members. ClubDistrict may also enable Members to publicly display some Registration PI as an element of their Profile Information if they choose to do so via a profile setting under “Edit Profile.” Search engines may index the portion of a Member’s profile (including the Profile Information it contains) that is publicly displayed.

If you have consented to receive promotional materials (e.g., newsletters) or notifications from ClubDistrict, ClubDistrict may periodically use your email address to send you such materials related to the ClubDistrict Services, as applicable. If you want to stop receiving such materials from ClubDistrict, you can change your profile settings under “Account Settings,” or follow the unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

ClubDistrict employees, agents and contractors must have a business reason to obtain access to your PI. ClubDistrict may share your PI with those who help us manage or provide ClubDistrict Services’ information activities (for example, message board administration, order fulfillment, statistical analyses, data processing), or with outside contractors, agents or sponsors who help us with the administration, judging and prize fulfillment aspects of contests, promotions and sweepstakes.

These outside contractors, agents or sponsors may temporarily store some information on their servers, but they may only use your PI to provide ClubDistrict with a specific service and not for any other purpose ClubDistrict may also provide your PI to a third party in those instances where you have chosen to receive certain information and have been notified that the fulfillment of such a request requires the sharing of your PI. ClubDistrict also may share your PI with Affiliated Companies if it has a business reason to do so.

As described in “Notice” above, ClubDistrict may customize the advertising and marketing messages you receive on the ClubDistrict Website, or may work with outside companies to do so. Your non-PI and/or Profile Information may be shared with these companies so this customization can be accomplished. ClubDistrict prohibits these companies from sharing your non-PI and/or Profile Information with any third party or from using it for any other purpose. Anonymous click stream, number of page views calculated by pixel tags, and aggregated demographic information may also be shared with ClubDistrict’s advertisers and business partners.

There may be instances when ClubDistrict may access or disclose PI, Profile Information or non-PI without providing you a choice in order to: (i) protect or defend the legal rights or property of ClubDistrict, our Affiliated Companies or their employees, agents and contractors (including enforcement of our agreements); (ii) protect the safety and security of Users of the ClubDistrict Services or members of the public including acting in urgent circumstances; (iii) protect against fraud or for risk management purposes; or (iv) comply with the law or legal process. In addition, if ClubDistrict sells all or part of its business or makes a sale or transfer of all or a material part of its assets or is otherwise involved in a merger or transfer of all or a material part of its business, ClubDistrict may transfer your PI to the party or parties involved in the transaction as part of that transaction.

When a Member who is located in the European Union chooses to post Profile Information that will be publicly disclosed, that Member is responsible for ensuring that such information conforms to all local data protection laws. ClubDistrict is not responsible under the EU local data protection laws for Member-posted information.

#### SECURITY: CLUBDISTRICT PROTECTS THE SECURITY OF PI

ClubDistrict uses commercially reasonable administrative, technical, personnel and physical measures to safeguard PI and credit card information in its possession against loss, theft and unauthorized use, disclosure or modification In addition, ClubDistrict uses reasonable methods to make sure that PI is accurate, up-to-date and appropriately complete.

#### ACCESS, REMEDIES AND COMPLIANCE: HOW TO ACCESS, CORRECT OR CHANGE YOUR PREFERENCES REGARDING YOUR PI AND HOW TO CONTACT CLUBDISTRICT ABOUT PRIVACY CONCERNS

Whenever possible, ClubDistrict Members may review the Registration PI we maintain about them in our records. We will take reasonable steps to correct any PI a Member informs us is incorrect. If you are a Member, you can view and change your Registration PI, Member preferences and Profile Information by logging into your account and accessing features such as “Edit Profile” and “Account Settings.”

If you ask ClubDistrict to stop using your PI, ClubDistrict will honor that request while retaining any record of your PI that is necessary to comply with applicable federal, state or local law.

If you would like to communicate with us about this Privacy Policy or ClubDistrict’s collection and use of your PI please contact us at feedback@clubdistrict.com.
